As we all travel across the sea.
Raising our voices we take.
In the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices.
Now let's go get the sails all unfurled!
Here we are in between
the sea and the sky.
Ready now for adventure.
We're itching to try!
Get ready to roam!
So all aboard now we're set to go!
Set sail to the ocean so deep!
Ready for a truly grand adventure!
Well don't you think
that sounds really fun?
All this excitement is second to none!
As we all travel across the sea.
Raising our voices we take.
In the beautiful blue world.
Our spirits ready to go.
Everybody rejoices.
Now let's go get the sales all unfurled!
If there's something that
I just won't ever forget.
It's the way that I felt
when our journey was set.
Now I won't be scared as long
as I keep that feeling there!
With that, let us keep up the pace!
While enjoying every
trip from place to place.
Our timid hearts get the rhythm ingrained.
So let's keep going, adventure awaits!
So many treasures await!
So now let's raise our voices in pride!
Laughing out when they are found!
With all the riches in
hand, everybody rejoices!
Party on, cause we stand tall and proud!
Life is adventurous, be
aware it's dangerous!
Who's gonna be one of us?
And a trip goes on because.
We're the pirates of the mouse.
To the west, to the east.
Gotta find my way, sail away,
all the way to one piece.
Bring all your dreams with
you, now fill the void.
In your heart, spread your wings.
And believe that you can soar.
Just let the breeze guide the way.
Till you're ready to start up once again.
Now you're ready for more.
So many treasures away.
So now let's raise our voices in pride.
Laughing out when they are found.
With all the riches in hand.
Everybody rejoices, party on.
Cause we stand tall and proud.
That bastard!
Where's my shadow?
It ain't here, you idiot.
Take a look at where you are.
This is...
Yeah, the sunny.
Wait, but what are we doing
back here all of a sudden?
It wasn't a dream after all, was it?
I really lost my shadow.
This feels weird.
You guys!
This is an emergency!
Someone came in here and stole
all our food while we were out!
The guy with a mouthful of grub is
complaining that there's nothing to eat.
I'm mad too, but at least they
left the dried food behind.
Who cares about that stuff?
I need meat!
Bastards!
I screwed up.
How could I let this happen?
I really let my guard down.
They took our lunchboxes.
There's nothing but cheese. No fair.
Why cheese?
So where's Nami?
Is she waiting outside or something?
You let some bastard kidnap my angel?
Why didn't you chase them
to the ends of the world?
It's not really our fault, okay?
This particular guy is kind
of hard to catch, you see?
You tell me who he is
and where I can find him.
I'll hunt him down right
now and bring her back.
Wait, let me explain the situation
here It's sort of complicated.
Okay, so this is the deal you guys!
Even if it kills us we
have two big things that
we have to get back no
matter what food and Nami.
Oh and our shadows too.
That's three.
Okay, uh, I'm not sure if one
of those really makes the list
Food is great and all but let's
focus on Nami and shadows for now
He... He's...
He's going...
TO MARRY HER!
No way in hell!
Let me at him!
Wow, this guy must be pretty
brave if he wants to marry Nami.
And what's all this
about me being a monster?
Why does my shadow get
to do all the cool stuff?
So, Usopp, you guys already saw who or
what has Sanji and Luffy's shadows, right?
No one told me we were fighting one
of the seven warlords of the sea!
Can I just hide in a hole
and cry myself to sleep?
You guys were all business
just a second ago.
Hey wait a sec!
If you put someone's shadow in a zombie
they act like that person, right?
Then I think I've seen your zombies.
Oro!
Oh yeah!
What kind of guy was he?
Hmm.
Well he looked just
like you but since he was
wearing wooden clogs I
could tell it wasn't you.
So if we find this guy with
the clogs the dog penguin thing
one has Sanji's shadow and
Luffy's giant monster zombie.
All we gotta do is
throw some salt in their
mouths and then we'll
get our shadows back.
Is that it? Uh...
-huh, that's what it looks like.
Nice job on figuring out their weaknesses.
How'd you pull that one off?
Save your thanks for the afro.
Skeleton that only did he
know how to beat the zombies?
He also told us you'd be
waiting back here at the Sunny.
What you ran into Brook again? Yeah.
Though I feel a little bad
since I asked a pretty cruel
question even though you
wanted him to join the crew.
When I met the guy I didn't
give him a fair shake.
Truth be told I barely even
thought of him as human.
But once I actually took
the time to talk to him
for a second I found out
he has a real backbone.
Other than the obvious, I mean
that skeleton's a real man.
Hold on a second!
While you're still in a mood to talk.
There's one more burning question
I still need an answer to.
If you go out in public looking like that?
You know how people are
going to react, don't you?
I mean, you're a talking skeleton.
There's no way someone as creepy as you
is ever going to make friends with anyone!
People are going to run away in terror.
Franky, why are you telling him that?
Even if you could see the sun and
make it out of these cursed waters,
your life would still
be full of suffering.
You've had it rough for
a long time already.
Are you sure you could handle that?
After all, you said before that you were
so lonely that you wanted to die, right?
If I were you, I would have
given up on life a long time ago.
And yet, you still act like a gentleman.
You laugh, you sing, you pretend like
you don't have a care in the world.
What is it that's keeping you alive?
You said you made a promise to a friend.
What is it?
How could it be so important?
You're interested in me, are you?
The story is quite simple.
At a certain point in the past,
before we came to these waters,
my crew left behind a good friend of ours.
It was a troubling situation,
but we did it out of necessity.
The only consolation we
could offer this friend was a
promise that we would return
one day no matter the cost!
But then the crew was annihilated and the
promise that we made was left unfulfilled.
Since I am the only survivor,
it is my duty to return to our
friend even if I must bear sad news.
How long has it been
since the day we died?
I've lost count but it's
been more than 50 years now.
50 years?
You're talking ages ago. Here, hell?
I wasn't even born yet.
I hate to break it to you, buddy,
but there's no way your
friend's still waiting for you.
You don't know that!
But it's true that he would have
every right to leave by now.
I realize I may be foolish
to believe he's still there.
However, if by some chance he
did believe in our promise?
And is waiting for us even
after all these years!
then the loneliness he's suffering
would be far worse than my own.
How sad he must be,
wondering if we betrayed him,
wondering if our promise was alive, yet
still waiting for us in the same place.
You're right, but...
The name of that friend that we left at
the Cape swearing to meet again is...
Laboon.
He was just a child.
We simply couldn't take such a young
whale on a dangerous journey like that.
A whale?
Yes.
I can only imagine how
big he's grown since then
You think that whale
understood your promise?
In his own way
I can't help but think that he's
still waiting for us at that cape?
staring longingly at the Grand Line.
He probably wants to hear us play our
cheerful music again, dancing and singing.
Although, I suppose it's
a bit late for that now.
Even if I am able to return,
I don't think he'll forgive us for
running away and dying like that.
But no matter how much he resents me?
For forcing him to suffer
all of these years,
death is never an apology!
Because when a man makes a promise he
doesn't stop fighting until he fulfills it.
So there you have it
that's it the whole story.
This is crazy what are the
chances I'll be damned?
We've met that whale before,
and
we know
that promise.
You know him that's crazy
how is that possible
It was when we passed through to
the Grand Line at the two capes
The damn giant whale was
blocking the entrance
It was at the Red Line Grief drove him to
keep bashing his head
against the dividing wall
He spent 50 years waiting
for his friends there
believing they'd return
for him after their voyage.
I couldn't believe it,
but somehow Luffy convinced
him to stop trying
to break through the
wall like a damned idiot.
Even now, he's alive out there.
Waiting at that cape for his
friends to finally return.
It's an incredible story.
Talk about true friends.
He kept his promise to them
for more than half a century.
And to think, we met one of Laboon's
friends by complete coincidence.
Wonder what that
skeleton's doing right now.
I won't deny that you've gotten stronger
over these past five years, but so have I!
And remember, I already know
every move you're gonna make!
You care more about that damn
afro than the skull beneath it.
Too bad for you, it's the biggest
target on your whole body.
Shut up!
Laboon, I wonder, old friend, after all
these years, do you still remember me?
When I think of how alone you must
have felt, it breaks my heart in two.
Although, I don't suppose
I have a heart anymore.
The Couran line is so fearsome.
Believe me, I tried as hard as I could.
I tried to bring them back to you, but
all of our friends have passed away.
Not only have I lost our friends I lost my
face my body my shadow
everything I once was.
If we were to meet again
you probably wouldn't
even recognize me how
could you with me looking?
I don't have anything left, not
a single reminder of my own self.
Except for this hair on
my head black round and
funny just like you I
didn't notice it before.
But they kind of look alike Brooks head
is almost the same shape as Laboon's.
The two of you could be brothers.
I must protect it so
you'll still recognize me.
I'm coming, Waboo, just as I promised.
I hope you're still waiting.
Waiting for me.
I have promised Kate.
I love that bonehead in a stupid whale!
SHUT UP!
I'm so pumped, guys!
He's a musician, a talking skeleton,
has an afro, does that yo-ho-ho thing?
and he was one of Laboon's best friends!
Even if I've gotta force him
to, he's gonna join our crew!
We got us a musician! Any objections?
Speak up!
Would it really change
your mind even if we did?
I want him to join the crew too,
no question, him and Laboon.
Complete and total approval.
Take me here you big dumb bastard!
And I'm not scared of skeletons, dammit.
Before I can answer such an easy question!
I've got to put a stop to this
shotgun wedding of Narmies.
Hey Saru, where are you going?
Going off to get started.
You keep adding shadows?
We've got a lot we need to get back.
All right, crew.
Time to get serious.
Prepare for the counterattack.
We're going to put Thriller
Bark in a watery grave.
Yeah!
All right.
We've got our work cut out for us.
I doubt we're just
going to turn the corner
and find the zombies
with our shadows in them.
Not only that, Luffy Zombie
is a complete freak of nature.
He's six times bigger than any giant.
I'm not sure anyone could beat it.
It's true.
Well, we don't really have
to worry about the zombies.
Though I kind of want
to see how cool mine is.
What are you talking about?
You want to hide from the sun
for the rest of your life?
We've got to get our shadows
back from these ghouls.
Yeah, but there's another way.
You remember what that
geezer zombie told us?
I saw you fight those zombies.
All of you have such
unbelievable strength. All right.
So what did you want to tell us?
There's an evil man who
must be brought down.
And I think you youngsters
are strong enough to do it.
He's left a trail of victims in his wake.
If you defeat him, they'll all be rescued.
All we've got to do to free the
shadows is put an end to Gecko Moria.
He said that, huh?
Luffy, always gets straight to the point.
Up there, Gecko Moria's just sitting
on his big ass waiting for us? What?
Are you nuts?
What do you mean?
His butt's asking for a kicking,
so that's what I'm gonna do.
And then all the shadows will return.
Sanji, fire up.
You're rescuing Nami.
That's exactly what I wanted to hear!
That Invisible Man's gonna be the
Divisible Man when I'm done with him.
I'm gonna kick his ass into fractions.
Hang on, Nami!
I'm coming!
Oh, I forgot to tell you,
but the Invisible Guy?
Yeah, he spied on Nami
while she was taking a bath
What the hell'd you say?
Why'd you have to add
more fuel to the fire?
Do you not seem angry enough to you?
I feel like it's all my fault since I let
that creep take Nami
right in front of my eyes.
It's only right that I go with Sanji!
And also I'll do anything to
stay away from that Moria.
I'm worried about the skeleton
fighting on his own he needs
backup if Straw Hat beats Moria
before the skeleton zombie wins?
Then everything's cool.
Otherwise, I got to work overtime to help
Brooke and hold on to my own damn shadow
I'll give you some extra
backup with that one Franky.
I Want to see if this legendary
samurai he's fighting lives up
to his reputation or not if we're picking
nami's my top priority That's the battle.
I'd like to lend my hands
to and once we get her back.
We can all take down Moria as a team
You say it like it's no big deal,
but did you forget who he is?
He's one of the seven warlords of the sea!
Yeah, but so what?
Crocodile was one, too.
That's my point exactly!
Crocodile got this close to killing you!
I'm begging you to be careful!
Seriously!
I already warned you!
Your zombie is terrifying!
Terrifying!
Yeah, I got it, I got it!
I had enough to make one
sack for each of you.
A little concoction of mine.
I call them zombie death salt balls.
Ah, so this is what you
were whipping up earlier.
That's good thinking, Usopp.
All right.
If we're gonna do this thing, there's
one point I cannot stress enough.
There may be a lot of thick
forests on this island to hide in,
but there's no guarantee we can
avoid the sunlight at all times.
We're all only alive right now
because it's the middle of the night.
In other words, sunrise
is our literal deadline.
We have to get your shadows back by then.
So don't forget it.
It's imperative that
we're out of here by dawn.
I know exactly what you mean.
There's nothing worse than going
a whole night on an empty stomach.
We're going to make you regret you
even thought about taking our food.
You hear me, Maria?
We'll make him give back twice
the amount he took from us.
And before dawn! Yeah!
Wait, no.
Were you not listening to me?
I was saying we got to get your
shadows back by sunrise or otherwise...
Ah, screw it!
Cool.
This is one big ship.
You'd think it'd have a
better view of the sea.
But who needs a view when
life looks this good?
Close one.
It's settled.
We'll use this ship to
become king of the pirates.
What Zora's gotten himself into now?
He's climbed to the top of
the mast for some reason.
I couldn't tell you why.
Has he?
Hold on master. Just hear us out.
It just doesn't seem like a good
idea to us to work with such an
uncontrollable monster I mean the
guy is capable of destroying islands.
He's bad news, sir.
I just know it calm down He just
needs to be properly broken in here.
It'll be obedient before you know it
Yes,
it's all in order with all
that my command we can't be
stopped and we'll continue to
gather even more powerful shadows
Before you know it,
our undead army will be stocked
full of unstoppable special zombies.
We're gonna need a mountain of those
marionettes for what we have in store.
Hey, Hogback.
Leave it to me, master.
Dr. Hogback! Huh?
Emergency!
The pirates, the pirates!
What's the matter Hilda those
three pirates whose shadows we just
claimed they woke up somehow and now
they're coming back here with all
their friends what impossible no
one wakes up that quickly after the
shadow's taken i i didn't see it
myself but their friends seem to have
beaten them awake anyway it also
seems that they're in cahoots with
the humming swordsman that's
probably where they're getting their
information from the one thing i
do know for certain is that he He
explained to the pirates how to purify
the zombies and release their shadows!
What?!
All the zombies are
terrified for their lives!
The pirates have got them on the run!
The wild zombies, surprise
zombies, the zombie soldiers!
None of them stand a chance
against these maniacs,
even if they didn't have salt with them!
Our only option is to
call the zombie generals!
But if they manage to purify
them, then the pirates might win!
We need Absalom!
What the hell is he doing?
Uh, well, um, I'm pretty sure
his wedding ceremony just began.
And I'm also pretty sure that all of
the zombie generals are attending.
You mean all those idiots
are gathered in one place?
Oh, I almost forgot to ask
you something important.
Absalom wanted to know if he could use
your dance hall for his wedding reception.
Well,
I suppose a wedding is a special
beautiful event But tell me,
do you think this is a
good time for nothing?
I don't care how, but I
want that ceremony stopped.
It's just I'm one of his zombies.
So it's completely impossible for
me to go against anything he says.
Just let the stupid animal
have his wedding. What?
If I weaken the pirates with my ghosts,
the zombie soldiers can scoop them up
and carry them here like tossil kittens.
Just because they figured out the zombies'
weakness doesn't mean we need to panic.
I'll gather up their entire crew
and have them here lickety-split.
Go ahead and get some
marionettes ready for
the pirates that still have their shadows.
I'll be in my room if
you need anything else.
Come on, Kumasi.
Right, sorry.
Excellent.
She's quite useful.
What would we begin to do without her?
You know, if you wanted to be useful,
you could shut your fat mouth.
Like Kumasi.
Anyway, everything seems to be in order.
No reason to worry.
Ah, it seems that way.
Talk about boring.
So you're just gonna sit there?
Is it any wonder why
you're always so bored?
Well, I'm not bored
enough to bother standing.
I'll just wait here for Oz to get back.
Well then, may I ask a simple request?
Huh?
If it doesn't make any difference to you,
could I be second in command
over Absalom zombies?
Ah, Moria!
Where the hell are you? No, crap!
Get out of my way!
Hey, give us back our fun!
Which one of you is the sick bastard
that spied on Nami in the back?
It wasn't me, I swear it!
Show yourself!
You know, we might not even
need the salt after all.
Their anger's doing the job just fine.
I don't think they even
remember about the shadows.
Five of the pirates are
storming toward the dance hall.
Not only that, but there's two
more of them on the bridge below.
There's no way we can beat them.
I can't believe these slow stupid
pieces of crap managed to capture me.
The more I think about it,
the more it pisses me off!
I'm sure you developed a pretty
close bond to me after I saved you.
Feel free to call me bro if you want.
I'd rather get caught again.
Oh no, not good? What is it? What's wrong?
I don't even deserve to be human.
I wish I was a mosquito.
I'm so ashamed.
My soul is as twisted
as my curly eyebrows.
Hey, Luffy, Sanji, why are you
just lying there? What the hell?
What happened to them?
Those ghosts suck the will out of them.
One touch from them and
they break your spirit.
I know that much, but I
don't know how to fix it.
All right, Call, we betcha now.
Damn it. Here goes.
Blitzstar!
Run for it!
We'll never get off this
ship if they catch us, too!
The ghosts are catching up!
They're right behind us!
Now stay away!
Things are taking up enough already!
I'm falling!
Koza!
They're gone.
No, they're okay.
I'm sure they are.
That really freaked me out, though.
The stairs are completely wiped out. Crap!
Where's the rest of the building?
Something came crashing through.
Usopp, Sanjit, those zombies, everyone.
They all fell down with the stairs.
Their legs are twitching,
so I'm sure they're fine.
Nothing to worry about.
What I'm curious about is this thing.
Well, whatever it is,
it's blocking our path.
Sure is a weird-looking wall.
Damn it.
What the hell was that?
I think it was.
It's not made of rock.
Weapons left!
What the?
It didn't even put a dent in it.
Ah!
What the hell are you guys doing?
It's just a wall.
A big, pink, fleshy wall.
That's not a wall you moron!
That thing's loopy soppy!
No way!